Avishag Ilan



050 - 5345340



✓ Avishagoliel@gmail.com



M Portfolio

About me

Learning and user experience designer, with experience in leading E2E projects. Responsible, creative, with high self-learning abilities. Working in a dynamic environment that requires teamwork and the ability to think outside the box would be ideal for me.

Education

2021 – Today Direct track to M.A. for outstanding students in Instructional Technologies, second year, GPA 94

HIT

- AR interface design
- Creating an artificial intelligence algorithm for matching work teams

B.A. in Instructional Technologies GPA 92 2019 – 2022

15 courses out of the degree's courses were design related (approximately 500 hours).

HIT

- Web design and development using HTML, CSS & JS
- Educational games development using Adobe An
- Designing objects, images and icons using Adobe Ps, Ai
- Training materials development using Articulate 360
- UX/UI design for mobile devices using Figma
- As part of my final project, I designed and developed a mobile task game generator intended for tour guides of heritage sites with low technological literacy

2009 - 2007

High school education

"Harel"

Full matriculation and 12 years of study

Work **Experience**

2021 - Today

Instructional design & development specialist

National Fire & Rescue Academy

- Project management such as various digital courses for the HR department, logistics department and more, including tutorials, videos and quizzes
- E2E design of training materials, posters, marketing materials and presentations for conferences, the training department and the academy commander
- Design and development of content for courses, trainings and tutorials
- Creating a Decision-making simulator during emergency for firefighters and commanders
- Management of complex learning systems

National Service

2011 - 2009

Association for the Advancement of Education and Welfare

Working with at-risk children at an impoverished neighborhood

Specializations and tools

- Figma / XD
- Notion
- G suite
- MS Office
- Adobe Ps, Ai, An, Pr
- Articulate Storyline
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Product design
- UX/UI
- Instructional design
- Web design
- Projects Management

Languages